Guide to the University of Pittsburgh at Greensburg, Visual Images, 1889-2019 UPG.RG.60
ULS Greensburg
- Flash Drive (FD), 2009-2018; III.
  - FD 2, 2005-2013; 2.
    Cassell Portrait [Dr. Frank A. and Beth Cassell] portrait by C.W. Gibbons, 2005]
    UPG Ambassadors Induction Ceremony 2011 [includes: inductees; graduating Ambassadors; all Ambassadors (grad., return; new)]
    - FD 2, 2005-2013 (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 1, Box 1)
  - FD 3, September 2018; 3.
    Buildings [Facilities] Library Garden, The [A Memorial Garden and Meditation Area].
    [Flood] Tropical Storm Gordon, Sept. 2018. [UPG Campus scenes.]
    - FD 3, September 2018 (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 1, Box 1)
- Negatives (NEG), IV.
  - 1994-1995, 1.
    Millstein Library Construction
    Commencement 1995
    Student Carnival 1995
    Faculty Awards Reception 1995
    Student Awards Banquet 1995
    Humanities Day 1995
    Psi Chi 1995
    Miscellaneous
    Chambers Library and Carillon
    PGAA
    Clock Dedication
    Baseball and Volleyball Teams Teams 1995
    Baseball & Volleyball Awards Night
    Basketball 1995
    McWhinney Retirement Party
    - 1994-1995 (Museum-cabinet 4, Shelf 9)
  - 1996-1997, 2.
    Sports 1996-97
    McKenna Hall Addition
    Smith Hall Addition
    Millstein Library Roof
    Chambers Retirement Dinner
    Choir
    Misc. 1996
    Campus Buildings
    Grubel Library Picture
    Communication Honorary Society
    Student Award Night
    Spring Carnival
    Faculty Awards 1997
    Sports Banquet 1997
    Late Breakfast
    Humanities Day
    Lokay Retirement
    Commencement 1997
    - 1996-1997 (Museum-cabinet 4, Shelf 9)
  - 1997, 3.
    Bio Lab and Faculty Offices
    Lynch Hall
    Powers Parking Lot
    Pictures in the Library
    Chambers Hall Dedication
    Miscellaneous Campus Shots
    Summer Camps
    Tosatto Dedication
    Library Staff
    Tennis Court
    Freshman Convocation 1997
    Joe Lokay Retirement Lunch
    Cassell Dinner 9/5/97
    Sports Photos
    Computer Center Rededication
    M. Goldberg Lunch
    Student Government Photo
    Fall Festival 1997
    N. Scanlon Reception
    R. Fogle ("The U.P.G. Edge")
    Snowflake Ball
    Midnight Breakfast
    Staff Awards 1997
    - 1997 (Museum-cabinet 4, Shelf 9)
  - Pt. 1, 1998; 4.
    Reception at DeSalvo's
    Student Awards Banquet
    Sports Award Banquet
    Sprint Carnival
    Faculty Awards
    Physical Plant
    Refrigerator Addition to Chambers Hall
    Senior Plaza
    Graduation
    CHildren's Literature Conference
    Smith Hall Road
    Goal Posts
    Volleyball/Basketball Courts
    U.P.G. Press Staff
    Soccer Backstop
    Lynch Hall Chimneys
    Terra House Tree Removal
    Freshman Convocation
    Freshman Move-In
    Tennis Court/Volleyball-Basketball Court Opening
    Student Activities Recruiting
    Presidents Faculty Reception
    - Pt. 1, 1998 (Museum-cabinet 4, Shelf 9)
  - Pt. 2, 1998; 5.
    Sports
    Anades Art
    Fall Festival
    Renaissance Festival
    Staff (President) Award Lunch
    Ferguson Theater Dedication
    Sports Banquet
    Staff Luncheon (Pitt-Pat Awards)
    - Pt. 2, 1998 (Museum-cabinet 4, Shelf 9)
  - Pt. 1, 1999; 6.
    Inside Dorms
    Thaddeous Mosely Art Display
    Presidential Ambassadors
    Honors Convocation
    Spring Fling Formal Prom
    African/New World Art and Religion
    Student Award Banquet
    Society of Analytical Chemists Workshop
    Commencement
    - Pt. 1, 1999 (Museum-cabinet 4, Shelf 9)
  - [Pt. 2] [V.2], 1999; 7.
    Construction
    Village Dormitories [Humanities Academic Village] Groundbreaking 11/16/98 Construction Dedication
    Security Addition to Smith Hall [Security Information Center]
    Terra (Rosetti House Restoration)
    Rosetti House for International Studies Dedication
    New Bridge
    Dining Hall Change (Chambers Hall)
    New Entrance [Campus Entrance Way]
    Utilities Trench
    Long Distance Learning Lab
    - [Pt. 2] [V.2], 1999 (Museum-cabinet 4, Shelf 9)
  - [Pt. 2] [V. 3], 1999; 8.
    Miscellaneous Ducks Croquet Tournament Set-up Flowers Inside Lynch Hall Smith Hall Lounge Cattails Stained glass window Tents for dorm check-in, 8/24/99 L. Beeson, T. Zaleskiewicz, T. Boldurian Disability Workshop
    Chambers Hall Interior
    Independence Day Celebration
    Sports (1999/2000) Tennis (Women's) Soccer (Men's) Volleyball (Women's) Basketball (Men's) Basketball (Women's) Dance Team Cheerleaders Sports Banquet Dec., 1999
    Chambers Hall 10 Celebration
    Homecoming
    Student Activity Fair
    Snowflake Ball (6th Annual, 12/10/99)
    - [Pt. 2] [V. 3], 1999 (Museum-cabinet 4, Shelf 9)
  - 2000, 9.
    Miscellaneous Segura reception Andrew Stockey Segura leaving reception Planting at entrance Croquet tournament S.O.A.R. 2000 Flowers and fungus by library Black eye Susans and fungi Rossetti House Hi level bridge damage Recreation room and Fireside Lounge (Chambers)
    Hurriccane Carter
    Sports Men's baseball Women's softball Women's volleyball Men's soccer Women's soccer Women's tennis Swedish basketball Men's basketball TIp-off men and women basketball Women's basketball Dance Team Cheerleaders
    Westbrook Retirement
    Spring Prom
    Sprint Sports Award Banquet
    Student Leadership Award Banquet
    Freshman Honor Society
    Pat Schmidt Retirement Party
    Heart Walk
    Student Organization Fair
    Joseph Lieberman
    Staff Recognition Lunch
    - 2000 (Museum-cabinet 4, Shelf 9)
  - 2000-2001, 10.
    Entrance Wall
    Fountain
    University Courts
    Bridge by Entrance
    Behavioral Sciences Village Dorm (Also Village Hall Enlargement)
    Parking Lot by Mt. Pleasant Rd
    Natural Sciences - New Technologies Village Hall
    Capstone Lab in Smith Hall
    Formal Garden
    - 2000-2001 (Museum-cabinet 4, Shelf 9)
  - [Pt. 1], 2000-2001; 11.
    Scope and Content notes
    Miscellaneous Chancellor's reception 1/11/01 U.P.G. Players Indian Musical performance Fountain Daffodils Reception for Lillian Beeson U.P.S. Check presentation Mushrooms Children's literature conference Actors from the outside Staff Picnic Rotary scholarship presentation Fountain #1 and #2
    Spring Fling Dance
    Kadunce Retirement Party
    Waxwood Retirement Party
    Student leadership Dinner
    4th July Picnic
    Faculty Dinner
    Pitt Fest
    - [Pt. 1], 2000-2001 (Museum-cabinet 4, Shelf 9)
  - [Pt. 2], 2001; 12.
    Sports Men's tennis Men's basketball Men's golf Women's softball Women's volleyball Women's soccer Women's tennis Men's soccer Sports spring banquet Dance team Fall sports banquet Cheerleaders Women's basketball Men's basketball
    n.b. Also contains prints and index of names of players keyed to exposure number.
    - [Pt. 2], 2001 (Museum-cabinet 4, Shelf 9)
  - January - June, 2002; 13.
    Miscellaneous Salvation Army Presentation Quilt Physics Workshop Sparks Reception Siegert goodbye lunch Drainage pipe
    La Cultura
    Circle K Spaghetti Dinner
    Bio-Chem Labs Restoration
    Spring Dance
    La Tuna Singers
    "College Day" for Elementary Students
    Soprano Singer
    Children's Literature Conference
    Student Leadership Recognition Ceremony
    Helen Connors Retirement
    - January - June, 2002 (Museum-cabinet 4, Shelf 9)
  - July - December, 2002; 14.
    4th of July Picnic
    Student Activities Fair
    9/11 Ceremony
    King and Queen of Pittfest
    Traffic Lights
    Stairs to Robertshaw Dorm
    UPG Pageant
    Snow Scenes
    Staff Awards Lunch
    - July - December, 2002 (Museum-cabinet 4, Shelf 9)
  - 2002, 15.
    Men's Tennis
    Women's Softball
    Men's Baseball
    Women's Volleyball
    NCAA Acceptance Picnic
    Women's Soccer
    Men's Soccer
    Cross Country Track
    Men's Basketball
    Sets of Twins
    Dance Team
    Cheerleaders
    Fall Sports Awards
    Men's and Women's Basketball Tipoff
    Bobcat Mascot - Mike McConnell
    - 2002 (Museum-cabinet 4, Shelf 9)
  - 2003, 16.
    Spring Sports Awards
    Men's BaseballEN'S BASEBALL
    Cross Country (Men and Women)
    Women's Basketball
    - 2003 (Museum-cabinet 4, Shelf 10)
  - January-June, 2003; 17.
    Library Staff. Group Photo. 2003
    La Culture 2003. Lecture Series. Jan., 2003
    Phi Kappa Phi. Installation of Chapter 286, UPG. Mar. 16, 2003
    Honors Convocation. Mar. 28, 2003
    Spring Fling 2003. Apr. 5, 2003
    Dr. Larry Senor. Retirement reception. Apr. 8, 2003
    Student Leadership Recognition Ceremony. Apr. 16, 2003
    Commencement. Apr. 26, 2003
    Children's Literature Conference. May 2, 2003
    Valeria Kettering. Retirement reception. June 25, 2003
    - January-June, 2003 (Museum-cabinet 4, Shelf 10)
  - July - December, 2003; 18.
    Katzman, Stanley. 2003
    Parking lot construciton. 2003
    Quilt (35mm slides and 6 x 7 negs.) Aug. 5, 2003
    Freshman Convocation. Aug. 21, 2003
    Tom Kelly. Retirement reception. Sept. 3, 2003
    Faculty and staff dinner. Sept. 5, 2003
    Student activities fair. Sept., 2003
    Student Government leaders. Oct. 9, 2003
    Snowflake Ball. Dec. 5, 2003
    Donald Reilly. Retirement reception. Dec. 4, 2003
    Staff recognition luncheon. Dec. 4, 2003
    - July - December, 2003 (Museum-cabinet 4, Shelf 10)
  - January - June General, 2004; 19.
    Miscellaneous: Black-eyed Susans, Millstein Library
    Spring Fling. Apr. 17, 2004
    Road Rules [Real World/Road Rules] Ace and Rachel. Mar. 25, 2004
    Honors Convocation. Mar. 26, 2004
    Capitol Steps. Apr. 1, 2004
    Boldurian Project.
    Nieto [Reuben Alfonso Lopez] Reception. Apr. 2, 2004
    Cathy Schmidt Retirement. Apr. 5, 2004
    Student Leadership Ceremony. Apr. 5, 2004
    Millstein Scholarship [Friends of the Millstein Library Scholarship]. Apr. 15, 2004
    Commencement. Apr. 24, 2004
    Children's Literature Conference. May 7, 2004
    Photos of the Gazebo.
    Chartwells Appreciation Lunch [UPG Staff Association]. June 8, 2004
    - January - June General, 2004 (Museum-cabinet 4, Shelf 10)
  - July - December General, 2004; 20.
    Bernard Berry Retirement Reception 7/29/04
    Freshman Convocation 8/26/04
    Flagpole Dedication 9/1/04
    Student Activity Fair [Fall, 2004]
    Student Leadership Seminar 10/23/04
    Staff Awards Luncheon/Reception 12/20/04
    Snowflake Ball 12/3/04
    S.O.A.R. (Student Orientation and Registration) July, 2004
    - July - December General, 2004 (Museum-cabinet 4, Shelf 10)
  - Construction, 2004; 21.
    Gym Floor
    Bobcat Logo on gym floor
    F.O.B. [Faculty Office Bldg] Steps
    Village Hall Steps
    Sidewalk Repairs
    Chambers Roof
    Millstein Stained Glass ["Upward to the Light"] Aug. 2004 Includes 56 slides
    - Construction, 2004 (Museum-cabinet 4, Shelf 10)
  - Sports, 2004; 22.
    Basketball (UPG vs. UPB) Peterson Events Center, Jan. 31, 2004
    Softball (Women's)
    Tennis (Men's)
    Baseball (Men's)
    Spring Sports Awards May 8, 2004
    Soccer (Women's)
    Cross Country (Men's, Women's)
    Soccer (Men's)
    Basketball (Women's)
    Basketball (Men's)
    Fall Sports Awards Dec. 10, 2004
    - Sports, 2004 (Museum-cabinet 4, Shelf 10)
  - January - June General, 2005; 23.
    Student Leaders. Front Row, 1-r: Stephanie Stojka, Jamie Book, Sara Liberto, Stephanie Parzyck, Yardlee Kauffman, Azallyn Amprim, Ray Wenk, Casey Schall, Andy Johnson, Cliff Hughes, Andrew Bolk, Jaysen Bartko. Row 2, 1-rL P J Rey, Mark Striegel, Tristan C. Robinson, Melissa Brandt, Carrie Smith, Krissie Verenna, Jihan Allay, Paris Carter, Cory Nestico, Janze Keddall, Lacy Betters, Megan Walsh, Elise Roth, Jessica Tintera.
    Honors Convocation. Mar. 18, 2005
    Coach Ken Carter
    Student Leadership Reception Ceremony. Apr. 22, 2005.
    Spring Fling [Spring Dance] April 16, 2005. [Identifies names of participants by Roll and Frame #]
    Road [Paving Project. Powers Hall, Lynch Hall Areas April, May, 2005]
    Commencement. April 30, 2005.
    "Upward to the Light". The Dr. Paul Albert Chew Memorial Window. Dedication. May 6, 2005.
    Picnic. 4th of July Staff Picnic and Croquet Tournament. [held on June 30, 2005]
    - January - June General, 2005 (Museum-cabinet 4, Shelf 10)
  - July - December General, 2005; 24.
    First-Year Student Convocation. August 25, 2005
    Student Leaders. Row 1. L-R: Yardlee Kaufman, Greg Zenyoh, Jihan Allay, Megan Walsh. Elise Roth, Stephanie Parzyck, Allison Schneider, Carrie Smith; Row 2, L-R: Andy Johnson, Amy Newland, Travis Bankhead, Jessica Tintera, Amanda Kotvas, Victoria Woodhead, Aaron Slafka; Row 3, L-R: Paul (PJ) Rey, Tom Schubert, Andrew Bock, Joe Frambach, Tritan Robinson.
    Snowflake Ball. Dec. 19, 2005. Greensburg Country Club.
    Staff Awards Luncheon, Dec. 19, 2005.
    - July - December General, 2005 (Museum-cabinet 4, Shelf 10)
  - Sports, 2005; 25.
    Sports Awards. April 2005; May 2005
    Cross Country
    - Sports, 2005 (Museum-cabinet 4, Shelf 10)
  - Construction, 2004-2005; 26.
    Westmoreland Hall [Natural Sciences and New Technologies Academic Village Residence Hall]
    Chambers Hall. Dining Facility Enlargement [Hempfield Room]
    - Construction, 2004-2005 (Museum-cabinet 4, Shelf 10)
  - January - June General, 2006; 27.
    La Cultura. Jan. 14, 2006.
    Honors Convocation. Mar. 31, 2006.
    Student Leadership Recognition Ceremony. April 21, 2006.
    Commencement. April 29, 2006.
    Children's Literature Conference. 10th, May 5, 2006. (Includes: 10th Anniversary Dinner, April 4, 2006.)
    Mary Beth Spore Farewell Reception. June 27, 2006.
    Gerry Enlow Retirement Reception. June 28, 2006.
    Staff Picnic. July 4, 2006. [Held on June 30, 2006].
    Mary Louise Hill Farewell Reception. June 30, 2006.
    - January - June General, 2006 (Museum-cabinet 4, Shelf 10)
  - July - December General, 2006; 28.
    First Year Convocation. August 24, 2006.
    Caring Day (United Way). September 13, 2006.
    Student Leaders. Oct. 31, 2006. Row 1, 1-r: Greg Zenyuh, SGA Speaker of the House; Emily Nalevanko, SGA President; Krista Costa; Katie Bondarenka; Eric Durant; Megan Walsh; Tora Parente; SGA Parliamentarian. Row 2, 1-r: Amanda Kotvas; Jessica Tintera; Victoria Woodhead, Senate Secretary; Aaron Slafka. SGA Senate President; Genevieve Jones, Kabeer Sahni; Chris DeFiore. Row 3, 1-r: Benjamin Mann; Justin Karapandi; Jana Valentine, Advisor; Meghan Kyle; Ashley Czekanski, SGA Treasurer; William Schaeffer. Row 4: Jayson Minnich.
    Snowflake Ball [Snowflake Dance] December 10, 2006. [note: there is exposure number index of attendees]
    Staff Awards Luncheon. December 18, 2006.
    - July - December General, 2006 (Museum-cabinet 4, Shelf 10)
  - Sports, 2006; 29.
    Winter Sports Awards Apr. 2, 2006
    Tennis
    Spring Sports Awards May 12, 2006
    - Sports, 2006 (Museum-cabinet 4, Shelf 10)
  - 2006-2007, 30.
    Mary Lou Campana Chapel and Lecture Center Groundbreaking, Dec. 6, 2006 Construction, 2006/2007 Dedication, Nov. 13, 2007
    - 2006-2007 (Museum-cabinet 4, Shelf 10)
  - General, 2007; 31.
    La Cultura 2007 "Welcome to China" Jan. 13, 2007
    Honors Convocation March 23, 2007
    Student Leadership Recognition Ceremony April 20, 2007
    Commencement April 28, 2007
    Resident Assistants August 20, 2007 See Table of Contents in Binder for Individual Identification.
    Student Government Association. Senate. Aug. 11, 2007 See Table of Contents in Binder for Individual Identification.
    Student Government Association. House of Representatives. Sept. 26, 2007 See Table of Contents in Binder for Individual Identification.
    Snowflake Ball Dec. 1, 2007
    Staff Luncheon [Staff Awards Luncheon] Dec. 18, 2007
    Da Vinci Awards [Induction Ceremony] Dec. 7, 2007
    - General, 2007 (Museum-cabinet 4, Shelf 10)
  - Sports, 2007; 32.
    - Sports, 2007 (Museum-cabinet 4, Shelf 11)
  - General, 2008; 33.
    Martin L. King Celebration January 15, 2008
    La Cultura 2008 "Egypt" January 19, 2008
    Hillary Clinton Campaign Event March 25, 2008
    Honors Convocation March 28, 2008
    Student Leadership Recognition Ceremony April 11, 2008
    Commencement April 26, 2008
    12th Annual Children's Literature Conference May 2, 2008
    - General, 2008 (Museum-cabinet 4, Shelf 11)
  - Sports, 2008; 34.
    Sports Award Banquet (2nd Annual All-Sports Award Banquet 4/15/08)
    - Sports, 2008 (Museum-cabinet 4, Shelf 11)
  - [Academic Year] Student Life, 2009-2010; 35.
    Student Leadership Award Ceremony 4/17/09
    Women's Soccer 8/25/09 [Academic Year 2009/10]
    Women's Volleyball 8/24/09 [Academic Year 2009/10]
    Sports Coaching Staff 8/25/09
    Cross Country 8/27/09 [Academic Year 2009/10]
    Men's Soccer 8/28/09 [Academic Year 2009/10] Individual team members.
    Men's Basketball 9/12/09 [Academic Year 2009/10] Individual team members. 11/6/09 Team photo.
    S.G.A. Senate 9/22/09 Group photo.
    S.A.B. Executive Board 9/25/09 [Academic Year 2009/10] Individual member photos.
    S.G.A. Executive Board 9/25/09 Group photo.
    Men's Baseball 9/28/09 [Academic Year 2009/10] Individual team members. 5/6/10 Team photo.
    Golf Team 10/20/09 Individual team members.
    Women's Basketball 11/6/09 [Academic Year 2009/10]
    Snowflake Ball 12/5/09
    Dance and Cheerleading 12/10/09 [Academic Year 2009/10]
    - [Academic Year] Student Life, 2009-2010 (Museum-cabinet 4, Shelf 11)
  - [Academic Years], 2009-2011; 36.
    Student Life Softball (Women's 2/24/10) [Academic Year 2009/10] * Student Leadership Recognition Ceremony 2/23/10 [Academic Year 2009/10] Soccer (Men's) 9/4/10 [Academic Year 2010/11] Baseball (Men's) 2/12/10 [Academic Year 2010/11] Basketball (Women's) 11/13/10 [Academic Year 2010/11] Basketball (Men's) 11/23/10 [Academic Year 2010/11] *Student Leadership Recognition Ceremony 4/15/11 [Academic Year 2010/11]
    Children's Literature Conference Children's Literature Conference 5/7/10 Children's Literature Conference 5/6/11
    *Filed in UPG.RGs as Leadership Student Recognition Awards Ceremony [faz]
    - [Academic Years], 2009-2011 (Museum-cabinet 4, Shelf 11)
  - 2010-2012, 37.
    Construction / Renovation Projects 2010-2012 Baseball Field [Renovations]; Baseball Field Bridge/Road Project; Chambers Hall (video screens installed in Wagner dining hall and Hempfield Room; sidewalk); College Hall; Faculty Office Building (FOB) (L.A. Sears Office); Lyceum (new office for student services); Learning Resources Center; Millstein Library (patio, front desk renovations, psychology lab); Pedestrian Bridge (high-level bridge renovation); Robertshaw Hall (sprinklers installed); Rossetti House (code updates); Smith Hall (HVAC renovation); Softball (construction of a new softball field); Sustainable Office and Classroom Building (S.O.C. Bldg.); Gatehouse (Baseline for S.O.C. Building); Tosatto Bridge/Road Project.
    [See: UPG.RG.35 Ser.: Minutes 3/15/11. Facilities Update Report, 3/3/11. "Status on Current Facilities Projects".]
    Note: Negatives arranged Chronologically. See: UPG.RG.60.Prints--Construction Projects in which the images are arranged alphabetically by project. faz 9/13/12
    - 2010-2012 (Museum-cabinet 4, Shelf 11)
  - 2011-2012, 38.
    Soccer (Women's) 8/21/11
    Volleyball (Women's) 8/22/11
    Soccer (Men's) 8/28/11
    Dance Team 10/1/11
    Basketball (Women's) 11/11/11
    Tennis 2/16/12
    Softball (Women's) 2/19/12
    Faculty/Staff vs. Students Charity Basketball Game 4/2/12
    Student Leadership Recognition Ceremony 4/20/12
    Children's Literature Conference 16th, 5/4/12
    - 2011-2012 (Museum-cabinet 4, Shelf 11)
  - 1997-2003, 39.
    Faculty
    Staff
    UPG Advisory Board
    N.B.: There must be a roll # and an image # by the name for there to be a negative image. [faz 2/20/07]
    - 1997-2003 (Museum-cabinet 4, Shelf 11)
  - Faculty, Staff, UPG Peer Group Advisors, January 25, 2005 - October 9, 2007; 40.
    2005, Jan. 25: Sheet 1: Eric Exler, Patti Stangl, Elisa Beshero-Bondar, Roger Taylor, Christina Andrea, Heather Kabala, Michele Griffith, Mary Louise Hill
    2005, Jan. 25: Sheet 2: Kevin Laskey, Linda Soltis, Marge Ulery, Karla Zaar, Kristine Azzarello, Nicholas Barsic, Stacy Clemmer, Matt Luderer
    2005, Jan. 25: Sheet 3: William Rued, Tavia LaFollette, Dean Nelson, Jeffrey Rouse, Nancy Estrada
    2005, Oct. 19: Kevin Conlon, Stephen Schrum, Natasha Margulis, Jacob Deininger, Cynthia Genard, John Prellwitz, Ed Krisner
    2006, July 25: Security Group [photo]; individual portraits: Jaison Stevens, Steven Rossi, Robin Shuglie, James Prinkey, Simeon McClain, Jared Stern, Thomas Horan
    2006, Sept. 26: Millstein Library Staff [Group Photo] Staff photo taken upon the departure of Nancy Young. Includes: Patricia Duck (Director of the Library), Frank A. Zabrosky (UPG Archives Volunteer), Karen Gavula (former Millstein Library staff member), Clara Vana (Asst. Director of the Library), Jim Vikartosky (Library Specialist), Sandy Buehner (Office Services Specialist), Jacob Deininger (Public Services Librarian), Bonnie Chambers (Library Specialist)
    2006, Nov. 14/15: Sheet 1: Cynthia Vislay, Daniel Milberg, Randi Koeske, Alexander Graziani, T. Zaleskiewicz, Brian Root, Dana LaViere, Jana Valentine
    2006, Nov. 14/15: Sheet 2: Kendra Sims, Susan Crampton-Frenchik, Elaine Kelly, Beverly Poole, Dick Hack, Ann Rea, Kristina Pazehoski, Valerie Kubenko
    2006, Nov. 15/16: Sheet 3: Amber McAlister, Tim Ackerman, Kelli Maloy, Paul Adams, Todd Brown, Gregory Bender, Kevin Laskey, Brad Graham
    2007, June 7: Sheet 1: Denise Kerns, Timothy Simms, Sabrina Smith-Reed, Brad Swenson, Linda Wagner, Clara Vana, Dane Radaker, Curt Varriano
    2007 June 7: Sheet 2: Kristine Azzarello, Donna Myers, James Vikartosky, Kerry Manning, Jesse Wallak, Brad Graham, Linda King, Marie Seftas
    2007, June 20, Sheet 1: Karen Gavula, Sheila Confer, Diane Hughes, Sayre Greenfield, Joel Sabadasz, Julia Kurtz, Odi Kraisinger
    2007, June 29: Sheet 1: Mike Altman, Mark Greenwalt, Carolyn Royse, John Turack, UPG Peer Group Advisors: Danielle Small, Lauren Leljedal, Robert Trey Whipkey, Erie Rubin
    2007, June 29: Sheet 2: UPG Peer Group Advisors: Aaron Slafka, Jayson Minnich, Lindsay Quaik, Jarid Stonebraker, Brittney Saxinger, Keith Dohli, Nicole Keller, Samantha Sinay
    2007, Oct. 9: Sheet 1: Karen Antoniak, Karen Ricco, Dan Mudry, Stephen Murabito, Cynthia Paul, Brandi Darr, Crystale Fleming, Susan Hahn
    - Faculty, Staff, UPG Peer Group Advisors, January 25, 2005 - October 9, 2007 (Museum-cabinet 4, Shelf 11)
  - Miscellaneous, 1980-2004; 41.
    Millstein Library. Holiday Program. Dec. 3, 2004.
    Pageant [UPG Pageant] Dec. 2, 2004.
    UPG Performance Collective. Production: Fool for Love. 2004.
    Basketball (Women's) AMCC Championship Tournament. Champions 2003.
    Various unidentified and undtd [1980's? early 1990's?] images of events, buildings, campus sites, campus activities.
    - Miscellaneous, 1980-2004 (Museum-cabinet 4, Shelf 11, Box 1)
  - Film Strip [Film Negative Strip], 42.
    "Film of Campus" 31 numbered strips. (lacks #12) + 11 unnumbered strips which appear to belong to the same shot sequence. Images: Pitt Seal (Stained Glass), Exteriors/Interiors Robershaw Hall, Humanities Village, Fireside Lounge, Distance Learning Classroom, Fitness Center, Millstein Library, Bridge, Ballfields, Tennis Courts. [Housed in Map Case as UPG.RG.60.NEG --Miscellaneous--Filmstrips--Film of Campus.]
    - Film Strip [Film Negative Strip] (Map-case 1)
- Prints (PR), 1969-2014; V.
  - Advisors [Advisors Meeting], 1992-1999 (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 1, Box 2)
    1992, 1995, 1996, 1997, 1998, 1999
  - Alliance Francaise (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 11, Box 1, Shelf 1, Box 2)
    See: Oversize Prints.
  - American Heart Association. Heart Walk. UPG Participants in Walk., 2000-2006 (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 11, Box 1, Shelf 1, Box 2)
    6/4/2000, 2001, 10/7/06
  - Anniversary (UPG), 1988 (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 1, Box 2)
    25th